when I heard about the talent program
for the first time the first emotion was
just pure excitement because if
Microsoft comes with a new initiative
you want to jump on the wagon we're very
happy to join the talent H program it
helped us a lot in in finding the right
Talent we really see this as an
additional on our current training ship
as well so we can really elaborate on
everything together with the Microsoft
power so that really helps so now we uh
get a new opportunity to see people in
in a lot broader brances or Industries
this is finally what we've been looking
for a way where Microsoft as the
publisher was partnering with us to try
to find that next Generation Talent po
hi good
morning so I think the talent program at
4ps has been a positive one people have
been in engagement with me right from
the beginning but I think the talent
program is extremely well structured and
personalized the the mentors behind the
program uh have vast knowledge and
they're always accessible if you have
any queries and it's really a unique
opportunity so what I appreciate the
most about the talent program is that it
combines both element of practical work
and the theoretical aspects of the Erp
system business Central Dynamics with
the talent program you have a journey
you understand which topic you should
check first and which ones later and
then when you start deep diving into
more specific topics you have the helps
of experts that make everything much
easier it's really refreshing to have
such a guided program you don't feel
alone in it and you're with the
community I'm really appreciated that I
was selected into this
program